indieswebs.com 2014-04-24

# Privacy Policy | IndiesWebs

**Privacy statement**  
Indies respects your privacy and committed to maintain that. The information provided on this page summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your personal and financial privacy and also dealing terms with this site and Indies Services.

**Information Collection**  
We may collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our website or e-mail correspondence. We may collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve our Web site and better meet your needs.

**Use of Information**  
Before we collect any personally identifiable information, we will provide an explanation for the possible use of your data. The information you supply will be used by us to fulfill your orders for our products and services, respond to your inquiries, supply you with requested information the products and services. We may also use the information to inform you about new features, products or services from which you can opt out in future at any time. We Never will sell your information to anyone or let it use free other than Indies Services or any of its websites/ companies/ partners.

**Dealing with Financial Information**  
Indies never stores your financial records like credit card numbers or passwords of your online money accounts. We also never asks to send them by email or phone. All our payments get processed by secure payment systems directly and we never stores any of such confidential financial information.

**Other Important Information**  
This web site may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. Additionally, some of our Web pages may contain "cookies," which are data that may be sent to your Web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our server to "recognize" you when you visit our Web site in the future. Most Web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you.

It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information. 

We are reserving the right to modify this policy page at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications in these Web pages.

**Legal Status**

The site www.indieswebs.com is 100% owned by Indies Services, an Indian IT outsourcing and development company. It is Proprietary in nature as per Indian laws.  
 ****

**Indies Services**  
201, Shopper's Point,  
Waghawadi Road,  
Bhavnagar.  
+91 278 2560266
